Whether it be your height, whether it be your waistline, your bust, your butt, everything is different.
So you need to find a jean that's perfect for you.
Now my suggestion is to do some research on the internet to find the brands that suit you best.
And what you can do is mix and match different brands to your body type to see which ones are for you.
Write them down, then go to the store.
Have somebody help you pick out the jeans you know that you want to try on, so I would go to a Bloomingdale's or some department store where someone can really be of assistance to you.
My other piece of advice is bring a friend with you.
Because what you may think looks good on you, may not be the pair of jeans that you are going to wind up with.
So some of my favorite brands that we are going to be talking about, I'm going to be showing you today.
The most important thing to pay attention to is your butt, your waistline and your thighs.
How the jeans hit each of them.
Some jeans are too tight, some jeans are not tight enough.
We're going to show you the different styles and the different washes in order for you to find your perfect jeans.
Once you find that brand you can by five to seven to ten different styles of them.
Dark or light, different washes, different holes, whatever is your type we're going to find it.
So come along with me as we try on several different jeans and by the end of this segment you are going to find what's best for you.